[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "How important is the award process to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "is", "the", "award", "process", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "That's all I do this for.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "all", "I", "do", "this", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "That is what talks in Washington, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "is", "what", "talks", "in", "Washington", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Until they do, I don't think this goes anywhere, does it?", "question_tokens": ["Until", "they", "do", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "this", "goes", "anywhere", ",", "does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Well, that's right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Is this all good for him or is all the attention being lavish on Herman Cain good for Cain?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "all", "good", "for", "him", "or", "is", "all", "the", "attention", "being", "lavish", "on", "Herman", "Cain", "good", "for", "Cain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain", "Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Michael Sitrick, I mean, could you imagine despite all this someone like Herman Cain winning now the Republican nomination and potentially becoming president?", "question_tokens": ["Michael", "Sitrick", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "could", "you", "imagine", "despite", "all", "this", "someone", "like", "Herman", "Cain", "winning", "now", "the", "Republican", "nomination", "and", "potentially", "becoming", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "You know, if there is one thing that I've learned that you can do is you can never predict for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "if", "there", "is", "one", "thing", "that", "I", "'ve", "learned", "that", "you", "can", "do", "is", "you", "can", "never", "predict", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Sitrick", "Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Would you say to him you got to get serious now or continue to ride the storm the way that he's doing?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "say", "to", "him", "you", "got", "to", "get", "serious", "now", "or", "continue", "to", "ride", "the", "storm", "the", "way", "that", "he", "'s", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I think one of the things that may be appealing is his style, is the fact that he is the nonpolitician politician.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "one", "of", "the", "things", "that", "may", "be", "appealing", "is", "his", "style", ",", "is", "the", "fact", "that", "he", "is", "the", "nonpolitician", "politician", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, seven and a half hours of work today, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "seven", "and", "a", "half", "hours", "of", "work", "today", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "How much of that kind of detail to you is in favor perhaps to Conrad Murray or against him?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "that", "kind", "of", "detail", "to", "you", "is", "in", "favor", "perhaps", "to", "Conrad", "Murray", "or", "against", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Well, I think it's more a focus for me on how many of those jurors have actually been jurors before.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "more", "a", "focus", "for", "me", "on", "how", "many", "of", "those", "jurors", "have", "actually", "been", "jurors", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "And so, if we were predicting a time that might come back, are we looking at Monday now, Ted, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "so", ",", "if", "we", "were", "predicting", "a", "time", "that", "might", "come", "back", ",", "are", "we", "looking", "at", "Monday", "now", ",", "Ted", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Well, it really does depend on one of two things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "really", "does", "depend", "on", "one", "of", "two", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"], "PERSON": ["Ted"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "You don't just mean with a guitar, do you, Brad?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "just", "mean", "with", "a", "guitar", ",", "do", "you", ",", "Brad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "I mostly mean with the guitar unfortunately.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mostly", "mean", "with", "the", "guitar", "unfortunately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brad"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "You are a bit of a player, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "player", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "I guess so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "Do you still enjoy it, or does it become this dusty treadmill?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "enjoy", "it", ",", "or", "does", "it", "become", "this", "dusty", "treadmill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "I love it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "So, when he gave you that guitar, do you think he had this wild, crazy notion that one day his grandson Brad was going to be performing to millions of people?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "when", "he", "gave", "you", "that", "guitar", ",", "do", "you", "think", "he", "had", "this", "wild", ",", "crazy", "notion", "that", "one", "day", "his", "grandson", "Brad", "was", "going", "to", "be", "performing", "to", "millions", "of", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "CD", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "AISLEY: I think he mostly just thought that I would love it like he did.", "answer_tokens": ["AISLEY", ":", "I", "think", "he", "mostly", "just", "thought", "that", "I", "would", "love", "it", "like", "he", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "What do you make of what's going on with America right now, financially, sort of a battle for its soul for whatever the new American Dream is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "with", "America", "right", "now", ",", "financially", ",", "sort", "of", "a", "battle", "for", "its", "soul", "for", "whatever", "the", "new", "American", "Dream", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "What do you think of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "I think that the key is that people still -- they still look to us.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "the", "key", "is", "that", "people", "still", "--", "they", "still", "look", "to", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "I mean, isn't this a very important time for America, isn't it vital now that the right person wins the next election?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "n't", "this", "a", "very", "important", "time", "for", "America", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "vital", "now", "that", "the", "right", "person", "wins", "the", "next", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "JJ", "RB", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Well, yes, I think because -- although, I believe that there are more than -- there's more than one way to skin a cat.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "think", "because", "--", "although", ",", "I", "believe", "that", "there", "are", "more", "than", "--", "there", "'s", "more", "than", "one", "way", "to", "skin", "a", "cat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "There's areas where that has to happen, to just draw these lines and say I'm this or I'm that, that's where we're getting into trouble, you know?", "question_tokens": ["There", "'s", "areas", "where", "that", "has", "to", "happen", ",", "to", "just", "draw", "these", "lines", "and", "say", "I", "'m", "this", "or", "I", "'m", "that", ",", "that", "'s", "where", "we", "'re", "getting", "into", "trouble", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "WRB", "IN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "I want to play you the clip of what you said about President Obama, which is quite interesting, when he became president.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "want", "to", "play", "you", "the", "clip", "of", "what", "you", "said", "about", "President", "Obama", ",", "which", "is", "quite", "interesting", ",", "when", "he", "became", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Was that -- was there always going to be a slight end of the honeymoon, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "--", "was", "there", "always", "going", "to", "be", "a", "slight", "end", "of", "the", "honeymoon", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ":", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "I mean, that is a bit of a result isn't it, as they say?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "that", "is", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "result", "is", "n't", "it", ",", "as", "they", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Yes, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "How does your wife feel about the fact that you keep co- hosting with Carrie Underwood?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "your", "wife", "feel", "about", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "keep", "co-", "hosting", "with", "Carrie", "Underwood", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VB", "-NONE-", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "She's good with that.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "good", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carrie Underwood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "How many more times will you do it before doubts start to creep in of what's going on here?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "more", "times", "will", "you", "do", "it", "before", "doubts", "start", "to", "creep", "in", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Well, we also just had a big hit.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "also", "just", "had", "a", "big", "hit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "You've won how many CMAs there?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "won", "how", "many", "CMAs", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "How important is the award process to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "is", "the", "award", "process", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "It's all I do this for.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "I", "do", "this", "for", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "I know, I know, wouldn't that be something?", "question_tokens": ["I", "know", ",", "I", "know", ",", "would", "n't", "that", "be", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "It's a great moment.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "great", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Of all time?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Of all time.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "all", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "What made him special?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "him", "special", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Unique ability to sound instantly identifiable.", "answer_tokens": ["Unique", "ability", "to", "sound", "instantly", "identifiable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Would you really?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VBG", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "That good?", "question_tokens": ["That", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "She's -- she can sing -- and the beauty of it is, she could sing anything she wanted.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "--", "she", "can", "sing", "--", "and", "the", "beauty", "of", "it", "is", ",", "she", "could", "sing", "anything", "she", "wanted", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Which is great for the country music world, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "is", "great", "for", "the", "country", "music", "world", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Totally.", "answer_tokens": ["Totally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "I mean, is she revered now in the -- in that world?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "she", "revered", "now", "in", "the", "--", "in", "that", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Yes, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "ORGAN: For that kind of decision she took?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "For", "that", "kind", "of", "decision", "she", "took", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I think she is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Did he get to see how successful you've become?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "get", "to", "see", "how", "successful", "you", "'ve", "become", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CMA"]}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "What were you feeling as you -- as you got emotional there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "feeling", "as", "you", "--", "as", "you", "got", "emotional", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I'm keenly aware of the fact that CMA is -- that's our Oscars.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "keenly", "aware", "of", "the", "fact", "that", "CMA", "is", "--", "that", "'s", "our", "Oscars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "ORGAN: How many more do you want to snaffle?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "How", "many", "more", "do", "you", "want", "to", "snaffle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Don't need any more.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "need", "any", "more", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "It's totally true.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "totally", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Where were you watching the movie?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "watching", "the", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "I was -- I was 20 years old.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "--", "I", "was", "20", "years", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "And now 15 million albums later, can you believe it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "now", "15", "million", "albums", "later", ",", "can", "you", "believe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Still pretty much surreal.", "answer_tokens": ["Still", "pretty", "much", "surreal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 493, "question": "We've never actually had our dinner date, have we?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "never", "actually", "had", "our", "dinner", "date", ",", "have", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Hum.", "answer_tokens": ["Hum", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "WP", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I think oh, my God, what a platt (ph).", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "oh", ",", "my", "God", ",", "what", "a", "platt", "(", "ph", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "I mean, I love watching that because apart from the fact you seem so relaxed, the fact that you are just cavorting with one of the most famous television stars of all time, again, you must feel like pinching yourself, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "love", "watching", "that", "because", "apart", "from", "the", "fact", "you", "seem", "so", "relaxed", ",", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "are", "just", "cavorting", "with", "one", "of", "the", "most", "famous", "television", "stars", "of", "all", "time", ",", "again", ",", "you", "must", "feel", "like", "pinching", "yourself", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "I still get a fight.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "still", "get", "a", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "POS", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Do you ever ask how you're going?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "ask", "how", "you", "'re", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Every artist does have that wee bit of let's be the best.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "artist", "does", "have", "that", "wee", "bit", "of", "let", "'s", "be", "the", "best", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "ORGAN: So you've now gotten a little bit more now competitive?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "So", "you", "'ve", "now", "gotten", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "now", "competitive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "It's the name of the game.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "name", "of", "the", "game", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Quite adoptable, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["Quite", "adoptable", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "He is lovable.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "lovable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "What would your mother have made of this, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "your", "mother", "have", "made", "of", "this", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "That was a bit of a tricky one.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "tricky", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJS", "RB", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "What were the values she taught you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "the", "values", "she", "taught", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Christian values, how to put yourself in other people's shoes and how to give your best even when things are really tough.", "answer_tokens": ["Christian", "values", ",", "how", "to", "put", "yourself", "in", "other", "people", "'s", "shoes", "and", "how", "to", "give", "your", "best", "even", "when", "things", "are", "really", "tough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "And in that moment you must have felt I don't know -- how did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "that", "moment", "you", "must", "have", "felt", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "--", "how", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "A bit pleased.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "bit", "pleased", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "It's a happy ending.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "happy", "ending", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "They've contacted you and they said sorry?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'ve", "contacted", "you", "and", "they", "said", "sorry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Some of them have.", "answer_tokens": ["Some", "of", "them", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Stuff of dreams isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Stuff", "of", "dreams", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "It is, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Does it still feel like that?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "still", "feel", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "It does a bit.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "a", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny Osmond"]}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "What has been your biggest pinch me moment of them all?", "question_tokens": ["What", "has", "been", "your", "biggest", "pinch", "me", "moment", "of", "them", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "I think I would have to say meeting Donny Osmond.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "would", "have", "to", "say", "meeting", "Donny", "Osmond", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "You have a big soft spot for him, haven't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "a", "big", "soft", "spot", "for", "him", ",", "have", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "I certainly have, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "certainly", "have", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "Have you sang with Donny yet?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "sang", "with", "Donny", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Not yet.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "You sang for the Pope?", "question_tokens": ["You", "sang", "for", "the", "Pope", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "That was extra special.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "extra", "special", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Have you any idea?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "any", "idea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Maybe 500,000.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "500,000", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "You could afford to live here in Hollywood in some huge mansion, but that doesn't interest you, does it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "could", "afford", "to", "live", "here", "in", "Hollywood", "in", "some", "huge", "mansion", ",", "but", "that", "does", "n't", "interest", "you", ",", "does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "OYLE: I believe in being a normal person.", "answer_tokens": ["OYLE", ":", "I", "believe", "in", "being", "a", "normal", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "What's the next ambition for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "next", "ambition", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Ambitious to be continuing doing what I'm doing, continue to make people happy.", "answer_tokens": ["Ambitious", "to", "be", "continuing", "doing", "what", "I", "'m", "doing", ",", "continue", "to", "make", "people", "happy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111104pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Of the singing variety, right?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "the", "singing", "variety", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "It's from the album.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "from", "the", "album", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]